https://www.epicli.org/about-us/privacy-policy/

Senior Leadership
EPIC Family of Human Service Agencies, Inc.
EPIC Long Island wants to protect the privacy of visitors to our Web site. The information users voluntarily share with us will be used to improve the quality of our services, and to promote public understanding and education about the impact of epilepsy on people’s lives. EPIC Long Island has adopted the following privacy policy governing its Web site. The privacy policy is continuously being revised and we welcome your thoughts which you may send via messages to info@epicli.org. Users who have provided contact information to us will be informed upon changes to our privacy policy.
What personally identifiable information does EPIC Long Island collect from me?
EPIC Long Island respects the personal privacy of the visitors to our Web site. We believe that keeping your personal data private and secure is very important. Personal information is not collected, unless you voluntarily provide us with that information as described below. We do not sell or rent your personal information. We will not deliver target advertisements from others to you. We provide no mechanism for an advertiser to reach you, unless you sign up directly with an advertiser or outside vendor.
In order for the www.epicli.org web site to improve its performance and design, and to provide you with better services, we track the usage of our web site through information taken from our server log files. The type of information collected is basic statistical data, such as channels and sections viewed, time of access and amount of time, search phrases used to reach the our site, and browser type. This information is anonymous, and is collected in the aggregate; it will not personally identify you in any way, and we cannot get back to you, the user, through this data. We use this aggregated information in order to ascertain the most popular sections of our site, for general promotional purposes, and for making decisions about the future strategy and direction of the web site. The aggregated information may also be shared with third parties to promote EPIC Long Island services and the web site, or to add to general knowledge concerning the public’s need for epilepsy education and treatment services.
What happens when I make a donation online to EPIC Long Island?
You voluntarily provide us with personal information when you make a donation, subscribe to one of our e-newsletters, email alerts, request information about our services via postal mail and email. The information we collect through these transactions includes such things as your name, address, phone number, email address and when you make a financial transaction, your credit card number. This allows EPIC Long Island to send you messages and to share information with you that we think you may find useful, including announcements and invites about EPIC Long Island events and campaigns. We study our users’ demographics and interests which are voluntarily provided for a variety of reasons, including having better information on the needs of people we serve and how to improve our services. Should you decide not to receive email alerts, invites or information from EPIC Long Island, you can opt out at any time by calling 516.739-7733 ext. 155 or send an email to info@epicli.org with the words “REMOVE MY NAME” in the subject line.
How does EPIC Long Island protect my confidential information?
If you have shared with us your credit card number in order to make a donation, your credit card number is stored on a secure server and is protected by firewalls. EPIC LI uses computer encrypted technology to protect your information and this information is kept confidential. EPIC LI sometimes contracts with outside vendors and business partners to fulfill customer services and hosting services on the Web site. When we do so, we enter into confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements with all vendors stating that they will hold information received through our site confidential and will not sell or share user information to any third party or use the information for their own personal use. A very limited number of the staff of EPIC Long Island has secure access to data. We hold our employees accountable for our privacy principles and each employee is personally responsible for maintaining visitor confidence in the company.
EPIC Long Island may disclose information to law enforcement and other governmental or court authorities in the rare case when we are required to do so or if there is reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the EPIC Long Island’s rights or property, other Foundation’s users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
How are children who use EPIC Long Island Web site protected?
EPIC Long Island is concerned about the safety of minors who use the internet. We want you and your family to feel secure when visiting our site.
Do not send us any information about yourself or your family if you are under age 13 – including information like your name, address or email address – unless you have asked your parents for permission to do so. EPIC Long Island will not knowingly request personal identifying information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If we learn that we have personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information from our database as soon as possible.
Linked Internet Sites
EPIC Long Island web site has hyperlinks to numerous sites that we believe are of interest to people with epilepsy. We do not control the privacy policies of other sites to which we may provide hyperlinks, and the privacy policies of any of these third parties may differ from ours. You should read the privacy policy of other sites that you may visit through hyperlinks.
Where should I go if I have a question or a complaint about EPIC Long Island privacy policy and practices?
If you have any additional questions about your privacy on the EPIC Long Island’s Web site, or if you believe that your privacy may have been violated, please feel free to contact us at info@epicli.org.
About Us
News & Resources
Program Services
Careers
Fundraising
Contact Us
DONATE NOW
Privacy & Policy
EPIC Family of Human Service Agencies, Inc.
